snapmylife.com 2012-06-20

# Privacy Policy - Snap MyLife

## Privacy Policy

### 1\. Introduction

This Privacy Policy discloses and covers all of the privacy practices of Snap MyLife, Inc. and it affiliates and subsidiaries (collectively “Snap MyLife, Inc.”), including as they relate to Snap MyLife, Inc.’s website and related services (collectively, the “Site”). In this Privacy Policy, “we”, “us”, “our” and other similar references mean Snap MyLife and “you” and “your” and other similar references mean a specific user of the Site.

We understand and respect the privacy concerns of our users, and we have made it a critical focus of the Site to protect the confidentiality and security of the personal information you provide us. We have created this Privacy Policy to inform you about how we collect, use and share your personal information, and our privacy practices.

PLEASE READ THIS PRIVACY POLICY CAREFULLY. BY ACCESSING OR USING THE SITE, YOU ACKNOWLEDGE THAT YOU HAVE READ, UNDERSTAND, AND AGREE TO BE BOUND TO ALL THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY (AND OUR TERMS OF USE). IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THESE TERMS AND CONDITIONS, PLEASE EXIT THIS PAGE AND DO NOT ACCESS OR USE THE SITE.

### 2\. The Information We Collect

We may collect two types of information: Personally Identifiable Information (“PII”) and Non-Personally Identifiable Information (“Non-PII).

PII is information that identifies a specific user of the Site. When you engage in certain activities on the Site, such as when you register to use the Site, we may ask you to provide certain information about yourself that we will collect and store. You do not have to engage in the activities in which we ask you to provide such information. But if you choose to do so, we may ask you to provide certain personal information, such as your first and last name, gender, email address or date of birth. Depending on what activity you are engaged in, some of the information that we request will be identified as mandatory or as voluntary. If you do not provide the mandatory information for a particular activity that requires it, you will not be permitted to engage in that activity.

Non-PII is information that identifies your computer and its navigational patterns through the Site (but not a specific user). We may automatically collect Non-PII information when you visit the Site, through the use of a variety of tools including cookies (small text files that are stored on a user’s computer for record-keeping purposes and which contains information about that user’s computer), or other available data analysis or collection technologies.

### 3\. How We Use and Share Information

We use the information we collect to (a) provide the services you request; (b) notify you of promotions, special events, new services and special offers; (c) improve our product offerings, customer service and overall experience; (d) improve the content, operation, appearance and utility of the Site; (e) conduct surveys, research and evaluations; (f) troubleshoot and resolve disputes; (g) gather demographic data and (h) accomplish other administrative tasks.

We may share your information collected on the Site with our subsidiaries and other affiliated companies, and with other vendors and business partners, including marketing partners, with whom we work (collectively, “Our Affiliates”). Such business partners include companies who provide business services to us or on our behalf such as to market products or services to you, monitor Site activity, serve Site content, help to maintain our customer database, administer e-mails, surveys or other contests. We also reserve the right to disclose your information in good faith as required by law, in response to legal process including law enforcement requests, with any person or entity that has acquired all or any part of our business or assets, and where needed to prevent fraud and to protect the safety, property, or legal rights of users of the Site or Our Affiliates.

### 4\. Unsubscribe or Opt Out

If you decide that you are no longer interested in receiving email communications from us, you may follow the instructions in our emails to unsubscribe from our email list or esupport@snapmylife.com.

You may also revoke consent at any time for any use of PII, including user location information, collected from you under this Privacy Policy. To revoke consent, indicate by sending an email to the address esupport@snapmylife.com, with the word 'revoke' in the subject line.

### 5\. Privacy Policy of Third Parties

This Privacy Policy only addresses the use, storage and disclosure of information that we collect from you. Other websites, such as websites you may have clicked-on that directed you to the Site or websites that may be accessible to you by clicking-through the Site, have their own privacy policies regarding data collection, use and disclosure practices. If you visit any such website, we encourage you to review that website’s privacy policy. We are not responsible for the policies or practices of third parties.

### 6\. Editing and Requesting Your Information

We will permit you to change your profile settings. Even after you remove your information from your profile, copies of your information may remain viewable elsewhere to the extent it has been shared with others or it was copied or stored by other users. We may also be required to retain your information by law or for legitimate business purposes, such as to prevent identity theft or other misconduct.

We will permit you to request a copy of your PII that we have collected about you by contacting our privacy manager at the address below. You can also correct factual inaccuracies in this information by contacting the same privacy manager.

### 7\. Storage and Security

We believe the security of your information is a serious issue and we are committed to protecting the information we receive from you. We use commercially reasonable security measures to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of your information under our control. Notwithstanding such measures, please be aware that no security measures are perfect or impenetrable, and we cannot guarantee the security of any information transmitted to or from the Site. We also are not responsible for the actions of any third parties that may receive any such information.

We will retain PII, including user location information, only as long as our business needs require. We will then destroy or render unreadable any such information upon disposal.

### 8\. Miscellaneous Privacy Issues

We do not collect or maintain information from anyone known by us to be under the age of 13, and no part of the Site is designed to attract anyone under the age of 18. Children under the age of 18 may only use the Site under the supervision and direction of a parent or legal guardian. Such parent or legal guardian covenants and agrees to cause said minor to adhere to all of the provisions of this Privacy Policy and shall indemnify Snap My Life, Inc. and our respective successors and assigns, from and against any and all liability arising out of the use by said minor under his or her supervision and direction.

### 9\. Changes to Privacy Policy

We may change this Privacy Policy at any time. The revised Privacy Policy will be effective immediately when posted on the Site. It is the responsibility of each user to review the Site and the Privacy Policy periodically to learn of any revisions to this Privacy Policy. Your continued use of the Site after the effectiveness of such revisions will constitute your acknowledgment and acceptance of the terms of the revised Privacy Policy, provided that it does not authorize the use of your PII for a new or materially different purpose.

If you have any comments or questions regarding our Privacy Policy, or to report abuse of any PII collected under this Privacy Policy, please email us at esupport@snapmylife.com or contact us at Snap My Life, Inc., 3490 US Highway 1, Building 16, Princeton, NJ 08540. For more information about protecting your privacy, you may wish to visit: http://www.ftc.gov.

Last Updated: [Feburary 13th, 2012]
